This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will come a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally arrived at Marineford to rescue his brother Ace.
Inside the bay, the Whitebeard Pirates are fighting their way toward the scaffold,
but the navy stands in their way.
Meanwhile, at the bay head, the pacifistas launch a merciless attack on the allied pirates,
hell-bent on slaughtering every last one of them.
I'm serious! This battle is a fake! Just ask him!
I know about your treacherous deal with the navy!
You have their assurance that Ace and all of your pirates won't even get scratched!
They'll just go after your allies!
Forty-three captains fight beside you, and you handed us all to the navy!
Just to protect Roger's son!
I don't know if you realize the magnitude of what you've just done.
Squared!
You thrust a sword into your father's body trying to kill him!
You've lost your way, my poor stupid son!
But I still love you, even if you are a damn fool.
So, squad, please treat him kindly.
I don't love Ace more than any other son of mine.
On that you have my word.
Every single one of you is part of my family.
He hasn't changed one bit, the bastard!
But that crafty old snake gave us a pretty good shake-up, didn't he?
But to even suggest that I'd sell out my sons is ridiculous!
They can leave now.
He destroyed the ice wall.
He's a sharp one.
If you're a true pirate, then you choose which path to take on your own!
Those of you who'll still follow me, put your lives on the line!
Get ready, man!
He's coming his way!
The strongest pirate of the world!
The encircling walls activated.
The Whitebeard Pirates backed into a corner.
Need them to bleed into a tried one.
The WEIRD Pirates
The Unexίαςic
For fun!
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh!
The новых rebels!
Oh man, here he comes!
We're with you all the way, Pop!
Clear a path, let's do this!
Don't let them get any closer!
Fire!
He's too strong!
Activating the encircling wall!
Just get it done already!
Right!
What's the matter?
Uh, it seems that the wall is jammed beneath the ice!
Then fix it somehow!
Yes, sir!
Why are you doing this?
Damn it!
I don't understand anything anymore!
I bought that story, hook, line, and sinker.
Even though he was from the Navy, I trusted him over Pop's.
I was jealous, I was scared, but I knew he was right!
So why?
Why is Pop's still trying to save us?
Why didn't he just give us up and let us die when he had the chance?
That wasn't supposed to happen!
He swore to me Pop's would betray us!
Damn you, squad!
How the hell could he let the Navy trick him into stabbing Pop's?
Does that fool really think he would turn on us?
How could you do this?
Think of how Pop's must feel!
If I was lied to...
Then what I've done...
What I've done to Pop's...
It's unforgivable!
I'm so sorry, Pop's!
Forgive me, Ace, please!
Hey, squad!
Pull it together.
Tears won't fix what you've done.
Bastards!
How low are they willing to sink?
That old man's tough! He gets stabbed and he's still at it!
I gotta get serious and save Ace!
Off we go!
Hey, Jinbei!
Doesn't that strike you as odd?
They all abandoned their posts and retreated to the plaza while we weren't looking!
Hmm...
Indeed, that is a bit troubling.
But old Whitefeard has joined the fray now.
That ought to put our worries to rest.
True!
We can handle whatever dirty tricks they throw at us!
If I aren't the walls up!
I'm sorry, sir. We're trying.
But the ice is a lot thicker than we thought!
Fire!
Aah!
Hey! Are you okay?
Leave me here! Just go!
Hey, are you okay?
Leave me here.
Just go.
I'll make you pay!
The wall is the crux of our plan.
This is bad.
I'm going to buy us some time until they fix it.
That's as far as you're going to get.
You'll never reach the plaza.
Run!
Vice Admiral John Giant is attacking!
You're blocking my view.
Move.
What did he do?
Vice Admiral!
What?
Why's the ground tilting?
Everyone keep your distance from Pops!
It's even worse than an earthquake!
Just as I feared.
This can't be real.
This is insane.
It's not just the island.
The entire sea is tilting!
That old SOB sure got some style.
It's still a littleible孔ou.
I like it.
Oh no!
I like it!
I've got you.
Jinbei!
Hang on, I'll pull you up.
Thanks, Jinbei. I owe you again.
Thank me when this is over.
Is that crazy old man trying to get his own crew killed?
No, his crew was ready. They're used to this kind of thing.
I need help!
Hey, are you alright?
I feel like I survived the end of the world.
Huh?
What the...
One man did this?
He really is the strongest pirate alive.
I've never seen such fierce a power before.
But...
In the name of the absolute justice I've sworn to uphold...
I'd rather die than let you pass through here!
Here!
It's headed right for us!
The shockwave's gonna hit the scaffold!
Yeah! Tear it apart!
What happened?
It looked like a direct hit!
What happened? It looked like a direct hit!
But did we get it?
Did we get it?
Doesn't look like it even touched the wall!
Yeah!
What happened?
It looked like a direct hit!
But did we get it?
What happened? It looked like a direct hint.
Doesn't look like it even touched the scaffold.
So did something block the blast?
Do you see that?
It's the three admirals!
This mess wouldn't have happened if the walls were ready.
Whose fault is that? Your ice is blocking them.
Sure, but you could have just melted the ice, couldn't you?
Holy crap. I knew they were strong, but to repel that shockwave?
Don't give up, men. Not now!
Commander Jozu!
I say we charge the bastards while they're still reeling from the blast.
Are you with me?
Pops knocked open a window for us, so we better not squander it.
Let's go! Give them hell, Whitebeard Pirates!
Take her down!
Sounds like they're pretty pissed off down there.
Scary.
I want an update on the walls.
Uh, they're still down.
Endeavor, the energy that's flowing into the city.
Pump every ounce of power into the walls.
Sir, right away.
Almost there, Ace!
Luffy!
I'm coming for you!
I'll save you!
Activating full power!
What is that?
What?
The walls!
They've closed us in!
What the hell's going on?
Take that!
Will did it break?
What?
Oh man, not a scratch.
That's gotta be some seriously thick steel.
I don't know about you guys, but I'm pretty sure these are the walls they were talking about.
Come on!
Are you too scared to fight us?
Hey, look up there!
They've got an arsenal of cannons locked on us!
We gotta run!
They've got us locked in.
There isn't any place for us to...
Except there.
What's going on down there?
Why didn't the last wall raise?
Well, it's, uh...
It's Orr's body.
The walls don't seem strong enough to lift it, sir.
Also, it looks like his blood is running into the system and making it malfunction.
Damn beast.
Orr's...
You saved them.
Now, that's a noble death.
He may be dead, but he's still fighting.
Impressive, huh?
Huh?
You've given us a chance, Orr's.
We must be swift.
You know what to do, Aka'inu.
I'm the best.
Eat your volcano.
No!
Holy crap!
It's lava!
I'm not feeling good about this!
They vanished.
Now what?
Do you guys hear that?
That's it! We're finished!
Aaaahhh!
They've got nowhere to run.
Now we'll melt that ice and drown them all!
That's it!
Aaaahhh!
The White Beard Pirates are trapped in the bay held there by Akainu's magma.
With navy fire on all sides, they climb over Orr's Jr.'s body in hopes of pushing forward.
In the midst of this chaos, the order for Ace's execution is given, and Luffy makes a drastic decision.
On the next One Piece! Execution order issued!
Break through the encircling walls!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
nachft depending the automat size and the jundLE
Which there will be any сохран이네
If you're within a single unit of wnesta
I'll really like the correction that adds a fri-
I'm gonna be happy with it
I'm gonna cause an nen
To be